const data = [
  {
    question:
      "An 18-year-old male lacerates the penile uretha in the bulb of the penis. Urine has extravasated from the uretha into areas that are covered by a continuation of the fascia over the bulb. Where might the extravasated urine be found?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "In the ischional fossa",
      "In the medial thigh",
      "In the gluteal region",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "In the anterior abdominal wall",
    explanation:
      "Laceration of the penile urethra may result in the extravasation of urine into the superficial perineal pouch and on to the anterior abdominal wall.",
  },

  {
    question:
      "A pregnant female undergoes a pudental nerve block to reduce pain during labor and delivery. What might the patient experience as a result of this procedure?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "An inability to contract and empty the bladder",
      "An inability to perceive bladder fullness",
      "An inability to empty the rectum",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Weakness of the voluntary sphincter of the bladder",
    explanation:
      "The sphincter urethrae muscle, the only choice innervated by the pudendal, which contracts to maintain urinary continence, will be weakened.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A pregnant female undergoes a pudental nerve block to reduce pain during labor and delivery. What is the location of the anesthetized muscle?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Superficial perineal pouch",
      "Lesser pelvis",
      "Above the pelvic diaphragm",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Urogenetal diaphragm",
    explanation: "The sphincter urethrae is found in the urogenital diaphragm.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the weeks after delivery, a new mother develops a prolapsed uterus. What structure most likely was weakened during delivery and resulted in this condition?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Piriformis muscle",
      "Suspensory ligament",
      "Sacropinous ligament",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pubococcygeus muscle",
    explanation:
      "The pelvic diaphragm, in particular the pubococygeus muscle, helps prevent prolapse or herniation or pelvic viscera after delivery.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A 45-year-old man has problems with defecation, frequent bladder infections, and difficultly engaging in sexual relations. All of his problems are caused by spondylolisthesis of the sacrum, which compresses sacral roots in the cauda equina. Which of the following might describe 1 of the patient's difficulties?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The bladder fills normally but empties suddenly and completely",
      "The bladder contracts in response to a minimum amount of stretch, causing frequent involuntary reflex emptying",
      "There is an absense of peristalsis in the ductus deferens.",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "The bladder fills to capacity, but urine dribbles through the uretha continuously because the detrusor fails to contract and empty the bladder.",
    explanation:
      "The patient has an atonic bladder, these patients tend to retain a considerable volume of urine with a high infection risk and pass urine only as a result of overflow incontience.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "During prostatic surgery, nerves that are secretomotor to the prostate are lesioned. What signs or symptoms might the patient experience?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Inability to contract the levator ani muscle",
      "Altered sensation in skin of the scrotum",
      "Absence of peristalsis in the ductus deferens",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Impotence",
    explanation:
      "In surgical procedures involving the prostate, the cavernous nerves may be lesioned. In these patients, impotence, or an inability to obtain an erection, may result.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A mass has compressed a common iliac artery. To which of the following structures will aterial blood supply be unaffected?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Detrusor muscle",
      "Gluteus maximus muscle",
      "Corpus spongiosum",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Testis",
    explanation:
      "The testis is supplied by a testicular artery, which arises from the abdominal aorta proximal to the site of the blockage. All other choices are supplied by branches of the internal iliac artery distal to the blockage.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Nerves containing axons of motor neuron cell bodies found in the L2 segment of the spinal cord are lesioned. What signs or symptoms might the patient experience?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Weakness in the ability to empty the bladder.",
      "Absence of peristalsis in the rectum",
      "Weakness of the hamstring muscles",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Weakness of the internal urethral sphincter",
    explanation:
      "The internal urethral sphincter is innervated by sympathetic axons, which course in lower thoracic and lumbar splanchnic nerves, including L2. All other choices are innervated by spinal cord segments below L2.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A young femaile patient is driven to the emergency room and, upon examination, appears to be in a state of shock. She show signs of an internal hemorrhage. A vaginal exam reveals that the patient's cervix is soft. The patient indicates that she missed her last menstrual period and has a history of pelvic inflammatory disease. Your diagnosis is that of a ruptured ectopic pregnancy. Which is the most likely site of ectopic implantation?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Broad ligament",
      "Body of the uterus",
      "Posterior fornix of the vagina",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ampulla of the uterine tube",
    explanation:
      "The most common site of an ectopic implantation is in the ampulla of the uterine tube.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A young femaile patient is driven to the emergency room and, upon examination, appears to be in a state of shock. She show signs of an internal hemorrhage. A vaginal exam reveals that the patient's cervix is soft. The patient indicates that she missed her last menstrual period and has a history of pelvic inflammatory disease. Your examination of the patient reveals a palpable fluid-like mass. The mass probably contains the contents of the ruptured implantation.",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Omental bursa",
      "Vesicouterine pouch",
      "Broad ligament",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Rectouterine pouch",
    explanation:
      "In the upright position, fluid in the peritoneal cavity tends to accumulate in the rectouterine pouch of Douglas.",
  },
];

export default data;
